The first method is about getting the email account name.
첫번째 메소드는 이메일 계정 이름 획득에 관한 것입니다.
The method should return a string, which is the name of the account.
이 메소드는 문자열 리턴을 해야 하는데, 여기선 계정 이름이 되겠죠.
So far, the method signature looks good.
지금까지는 메소드 서명이 괜찮아 보이네요.
We have the access modifier, the return data type, and the method name, and
접근 제어자, 리턴 데이터 유형, 메소드 이름, 그리고
no input params.
입력 파라미터는 없고요.
You have a opening and closing brace as well.
여기 브레이스를 열고 닫는 것도 잊지 마세요.
The first line of code looks correct.
첫 줄 코딩은 정확한 것 같군요.
It returns a string in quotes, and then it has a semicolon.
리턴은 따옴표 안에 문자로, 세미콜론도 갖췄고요.
So, this is the return value.
이게 리턴 값입니다.
However, the problem comes on a second line when we see another return
하지만 두번째 줄이 문제네요. 또다른 리턴 문에
statement with another return value.
또다른 리턴 값이 붙어 있어요.
We learned earlier that you can't have lines of code after the return statement
이미 배운 대로, 리턴 문 다음엔 여러 개의 코드가 올 수 없습니다.
because those will be considered unreachable by the computer.
컴퓨터가 이를 도달 불능으로 간주하기 때문이지요.
So in this case, this method has an error on line 8.
따라서 이런 경우엔, 8라인에 오류가 있는 것입니다.
Okay, so let's do Method 2 now.
좋아요, 이제 메소드 2를 봅시다.
The second method is about adding $4 of tip onto the current bill.
두번째 메소드는 현재 계산서에 팁을 4달러 더하는 내용입니다.
The current bill is an input parameter, and the data type is integer.
현재 계산서는 입력 파라미터고, 데이터 유형은 정수형이네요.
The return value of the method should be the total price of the bill with that $4
이 메소드의 리턴값은 계산서 전체 가격에 4달러의 팁을
of tip included.
더한 액수여야 겠지요.
So let's check the method signature first.
메소드 서명을 우선 살펴 봅시다.
We have a access modifier.
접근 제어자가 있군요.
We're missing our return data type, so that's weird.
그런데 리턴 데이터 유형이 안 보이네요. 이상하죠.
And then we have the method name and one input parameter.
그리고 메소드 이름과 입력 파라미터 하나가 있습니다.
So the return data type is a red flag, but let's keep reading.
리턴 데이터 유형이 문제네요. 하지만 계속 읽어 봅시다.
Inside the method it says return bill +4 and semicolon.
메소드에는 bill + 4를 리턴하라는 내용과 세미콜론이 있습니다.
So this is the return value.
이 부분이 리턴값이 되겠군요.
Bill is a variable and we add four to it, so this evaluates to a single value.
bill은 변수이고 여기다 4를 더한 단일값으로 계산되겠죠.
And then that is an integer which should get returned.
따라서 리턴값은 정수형이 되어야 합니다.
So we're missing the word int right here.
그러므로 바로 여기에 'int'라는 말이 들어가야 겠죠.
And this is on line 6.
여기는 6라인이니까
So in the table we say that Method 2 has an error on line 6 and
표에는 메소드 2의 경우 6라인에 오류가 있으며
we're supposed to specify the return data type of int.
int라는 리턴 데이터 유형을 명시해야 한다고 쓰면 됩니다.
Let's look at the third method.
세번째 메소드를 봅시다.
This method is about setting up the app for our current city.
이 메소드는 자신의 현재 도시를 앱에 설정하는 내용입니다.
We don't have the code for the other app.
다른 앱에는 이에 해당하는 코드가 없지만
But let's just look at the code for this one method.
이 메소드에 해당하는 코드를 한 번 살펴보기로 하죠.
The method signature starts with private access modifier.
메소드 서명은 프라이빗 접근 제어자로 시작하네요.
And then it says nothing, which is weird because we haven't seen that before.
그리고는 'nothing'이라고 하네요. 이상하죠. 이런 건 본 적이 없어요.
And then the method name is called setup.
그리고 메소드 이름은 setup이라고 되어 있군요.
There's no input parameters and we have an open and closing brace.
입력 파라미터는 없고 브레이스로 시작과 끝을 지정했습니다.
Inside the method we see that there is a variable, it
메소드 안에는 변수가 하나 있는데,
looks like a global variable city name and it's being set to the string London.
city name이라는 글로벌 변수 같고요, 런던이라는 문자열에 맞춰져 있네요.
Okay, well, from everything that I've observed there's basically no return
좋아요, 음, 제가 살펴본 바로는 일단 리턴 데이터 유형이
data type specified in the comment here.
주석에 명시되어 있지 않군요.
It looks like we're trying to return nothing as the output, so
출력 리턴값이 없게 하려고 하고 있는 것 같은데
remember that the Java keyword for returning nothing is the word void.
자바 스크립트에서 리턴값이 없도록 하는 말은 'void'임을 기억합시다.
So I think the error is on line 4 here when we need to say void.
따라서 오류는 4라인에 있는 것 같네요. void라고 적었어야 하니까요.
Okay so I added that to the table.
좋아요, 그대로 표에 적었습니다.
Now let's move on to Method 4.
이제 메소드 4로 넘어가죠.
This method is about getting the number of students in a class.
이 메소드는 한 반의 학생 수를 파악하는 내용입니다.
The return value is the number of students which is an integer.
리턴값은 학생 수고, 정수형이죠.
The method starts with an axis modifier of private.
메소드는 프라이빗 접근 제어자로 시작합니다.
And then the return data type is an int so, so far it's looking good.
리턴 데이터 유형은 int고, 지금까지는 괜찮아 보이네요.
The method name is getStudentClassSize and there's no input params.
메소드 이름은 getStudentClassSize, 입력 파라미터는 없습니다.
Inside the method, we have the return keyword and
메소드 안을 보면, 리턴이라는 스크립트와 함께
then it says 20 in quotations, but
따옴표 안에 20이라고 되어 있는데,
this is weird because this is a string and we want it to return an integer.
이건 이상하죠. 이건 문자열이고, 리턴값은 정수형이여야 하니까 말이죠.
So the error is on line 7, where we have to return 20 without quotations.
따라서 오류는 7라인에 있으며, 리턴값 20에 따옴표가 없어야 합니다.
And this is what your table should look like.
표에는 이렇게 적을 수 있겠네요.